tinkertry.com 2012-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Tinkertry

This privacy policy tells you how personal information collected at [tinkertry.com](http://tinkertry.com/) is used. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for [tinkertry.com](http://tinkertry.com/) only.

**Collection of Information  
**Collecting of personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., is only done when voluntarily submitted by visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example, to add you to the [mailing lists](http://eepurl.com/fZ7Qb), which you may [unsubscribe](http://tinkertry.us2.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=0321e0e2cda1cb28cdf66b4ef&id=2232124c16) from at any time.

**Distribution of Information  
** We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology  
** The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

Google Adsense specific information:

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to [tinkertry.com](http://tinkertry.com/).
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
(Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

Here’s the full list of 3rd parties that [tinkertry.com](http://tinkertry.com/) uses, which may change over time, to help subsidize the cost of running this site. This screenshot shows the [Ghostery.com](http://ghostery.com/) plugin, on March 10 2012:  

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:
